Anna Klibanov

gobanana.ca / anna.klibanov@gmail.com

Over the last 15 years, I've worked across diverse industries designing and building software. My most scaled work was at Edsby, an education platform servicing over 215 million users worldwide and winning more than 70 awards. My passion lies in crafting functional and usercentric products, where I meticulously consider both high-level perspectives and minute details. My skill set, spanning creative, practical, and technical domains, gives me a unique approach to product design and management. I'm creative, adaptive, and love to learn. I am motivated by a challenge and love the reward of overcoming obstacles.

Work Experience

June 2010-Present Freelance Designer

GoBanana Design

- Extensive experience working with clients across all industries and media
- Worked with clients on small projects like single-page websites as well as large-scale projects including print and digital materials from concept to full execution installations.

Oct 2022-

Senior UX/UI Designer

Sep 2023

ActiveState

- Managed a design team to deliver low-and high-fidelity wireframes, mockups, and prototypes that offered exceptional user experiences
- Employed tools and metrics to measure the success of designs, conduct user experiments, and promote Product Led Growth
- Worked closely with engineering teams on the effective execution of the designs
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams and product managers in roadmap planning and setting quarterly goals

Sep 2020-

Scrum Master

July 2022

Edsby

- Led a 20+ person engineering team in Agile development
- Facilitated relationships with the Product Owner, business team, customer needs, and other stakeholders to ensure a clear and seamless product development process with best practices and usercentred design processes

April 2011-July 2022

Senior UX/UI Designer / Product Designer / Front-End Developer Edsby

- Developed UI elements and prototypes for mobile/web applications
- Constructed wireframes, user flows, low-and high-fidelity mockups, and prototypes for new and existing products and features
- Conducted market research and user testing/interviews to iterate through designs for the most effective solutions
- Collaborated with the engineering team to ensure implementation of designs and seamless product deployment
- Designed, created, and maintained all public-facing marketing materials across different media

2010-2011

Graphic and Web Designer / Front-End Web Developer

Ingle International

- · Designed and developed websites for clients
- Created intuitive user interfaces for web applications
- Worked closely with programmers to achieve optimal functionality
- Created other materials for the company and its clients, such as interactive flash presentations and print materials

Skills

- Product design
- UX/UI design
- User research and testing
- Wireframing and prototyping
- Web development
- Branding
- Project management
- Team leadership

- Verbal, written, and interpersonal communication
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Figma
- MS Visual Studio
- HTML/CSS
- Javascript

Education

2020 Certified ScrumMaster (CSM)

Scrum Alliance

2006-2010 **Bachelor of Design (Honours)**

York University/Sheridan College